Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
I really didn't expect that.
لم أتوقع ذلك حقًا.
That's way too overbearing.
هذا أمر مبالغ فيه للغاية.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Those people are just awful.
هؤلاء الناس فظيعون للغاية.
Gentlemen, your noodles are here.
أيها السادة، معكرونتكم هنا.
What are you two chatting about? So lively.
عن ماذا تتحدثان؟ نشيطان جدًا.
Haven't you seen the notice yet?
ألم تشاهد الإشعار بعد؟
Turns out The Rotting Chaos
اتضح أن الفوضى المتعفنة
was started by people from Yun Yin Mountain.
تم تأسيسها من قبل أشخاص من جبل يون ين.
They colluded with the eldest prince.
لقد تواطأوا مع الأمير الأكبر.
The main culprit, the eldest prince,
المتهم الرئيسي هو الأمير الأكبر،
has already been locked up.
لقد تم قفله بالفعل.
Tomorrow, the second prince
غدا الأمير الثاني
will personally execute those criminals.
سأقوم بإعدام هؤلاء المجرمين شخصيًا.
Such a big thing happened in the city,
لقد حدث شيء كبير في المدينة،
why is the second prince handling it?
لماذا يتولى الأمير الثاني الأمر؟
What about the City Lord?
ماذا عن سيد المدينة؟
I heard the City Lord is gravely ill.
سمعت أن سيد المدينة مريض بشكل خطير.
His life hangs by a thread.
حياته معلقة بخيط.
He has handed all Xuan Cheng's affairs
لقد سلم كل شؤون شوان تشنغ
over to the second prince.
إلى الأمير الثاني.
You just said the City Lord is ill—
لقد قلت للتو أن سيد المدينة مريض
is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Absolutely true.
صحيح تماما.
Eat your noodles, eat up.
تناول المعكرونة، تناولها.
Please, take your time.
من فضلك، خذ وقتك.
This is the taste.
هذا هو الطعم.
Yes, this is it.
نعم، هذا هو.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Princess Nan Zhengyue.
الأميرة نان زينغيو.
The second prince said
وقال الأمير الثاني
no one is allowed to visit these two.
لا يسمح لأحد بزيارة هذين الاثنين.
Please leave.
من فضلك أرحل.
I'm just here to see my brother and sister.
أنا هنا فقط لرؤية أخي وأختي.
These fine dishes and wine
هذه الأطباق الرائعة والنبيذ
aren't for them.
ليست لهم.
They're prepared for the three of you.
إنهم مستعدون لثلاثتكم.
Please, could you make an exception?
من فضلك، هل يمكنك أن تجعل استثناء؟
Princess Nan Zhengyue is with the second prince.
الأميرة نان تشنغيو مع الأمير الثاني.
There won't be any trouble.
لن يكون هناك أي مشكلة.
Princess Nan Zhengyue, come with me.
الأميرة نان زينغيو، تعالي معي.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Nan Zhengyue, why are you here?
نان زينغيو، لماذا أنت هنا؟
Second brother will have you executed tomorrow.
الأخ الثاني سوف يعدمك غدًا.
I came especially to see you both.
لقد جئت خصيصا لرؤيتكما.
Any last words before you die?
هل لديك أي كلمات أخيرة قبل وفاتك؟
That little bastard Nan Zhengci—
ذلك اللقيط الصغير نان تشنغشي-
he dares to execute us?
هل يجرؤ على إعدامنا؟
Who does he think he is?
من يعتقد نفسه؟
Bah!
باه!
If he's got guts, let him come himself.
إذا كان لديه الشجاعة، فليأت بنفسه.
I'll kill him myself.
سأقتله بنفسي
He doesn't know his place.
إنه لا يعرف مكانه.
Come, let's drink.
تعالوا نشرب.
Sister Zhengyue,
الأخت تشنغيو،
my dear little sister.
أختي الصغيرة العزيزة.
I knew our sibling bond was strong.
لقد عرفت أن رابطة الأخوة بيننا كانت قوية.
You'd definitely come to save us.
لقد أتيت بالتأكيد لإنقاذنا.
Enough talk, let's go quickly.
كفى كلامًا، دعنا نذهب بسرعة.
Go.
يذهب.
Go, go, go.
إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
Didn't expect you, little girl,
لم أتوقعك يا فتاة صغيرة
to have grown so bold.
لقد أصبحت جريئة للغاية.
Hurry, let's go.
اسرع دعنا نذهب
Go, elder sister.
اذهبي يا أختي الكبرى.
Sister, wait for us!
أختي انتظرينا!
I'm finally about to be free again.
أنا على وشك أن أكون حرا مرة أخرى أخيرا.
Zhu Sheng.
تشو شنغ.
Just let us go.
فقط دعونا نذهب.
Princess Nan Zhengyue.
الأميرة نان زينغيو.
Didn't expect you'd betray the prince too.
لم أتوقع أنك ستخون الأمير أيضًا.
He'll be heartbroken if he finds out.
سوف ينكسر قلبه إذا اكتشف ذلك.
Second brother has gone astray now.
لقد ضل الأخ الثاني الآن.
You can't make him turn back,
لا يمكنك جعله يعود إلى الوراء،
but you won't help him do evil.
ولكنك لن تساعده على فعل الشر.
None of you are leaving today.
لا أحد منكم سيغادر اليوم.
Take them all back.
خذهم جميعا مرة أخرى.
Stop right there, all of you!
توقفوا هنا جميعاً!
I am the proud eldest prince of Xuan Cheng.
أنا الأمير الأكبر الفخور لـ Xuan Cheng.
I've been living like a rat lately.
لقد كنت أعيش مثل الفأر في الآونة الأخيرة.
I'm done putting up with it.
لقد انتهيت من تحمل هذا الأمر.
Worst case,
في أسوأ الأحوال،
I'll fight you all today.
سأقاتلكم جميعا اليوم.
Qier!
أكثر!
Sis, I've been shot!
أختي لقد تم إطلاق النار علي!
It hurts.
إنه يؤلمني.
Qier!
أكثر!
Elder sister, I don't want to die!
أختي الكبرى لا أريد أن أموت!
It's okay, I'm here.
لا بأس، أنا هنا.
Eldest prince Nan Zhengqi,
الأمير الأكبر نان تشنغكي,
Princess Nan Zhengyan,
الأميرة نان زينجيان,
attempted to escape and kidnapped Princess Nan Zhengyue.
حاول الهروب واختطف الأميرة نان تشنغيو.
With ill intent.
مع سوء النية.
Stop! You can't do this!
توقف! لا يمكنك فعل هذا!
Release the arrows!
أطلق السهام!
Elder sister!
أختي الكبرى!
Qier!
أكثر!
Big brother!
الاخ الاكبر!
Elder sister!
أختي الكبرى!
Come, second prince.
تعال أيها الأمير الثاني.
To our soon-to-be great achievement,
إلى إنجازنا العظيم الذي سوف يتحقق قريبًا،
cheers!
هتافات!
Since you're here,
بما أنك هنا،
come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
It's done.
لقد تم ذلك.
Dong Qing is already lying in the stone coffin in the mist cave.
دونغ تشينغ مستلقي بالفعل في التابوت الحجري في كهف الضباب.
If you don't believe me,
إذا كنت لا تصدقني،
go see for yourself.
اذهب وانظر بنفسك.
Truly, sibling bonds run deep.
في الحقيقة، الروابط بين الأخوة عميقة جدًا.
Where's the greenfish stone?
أين حجر السمكة الخضراء؟
Enough for half a month.
يكفي لنصف شهر.
You should know better.
ينبغي عليك أن تعرف بشكل أفضل.
Come.
يأتي.
The greatest poison master in the world—
أعظم سيد السموم في العالم
just an empty title.
مجرد عنوان فارغ.
Nothing but a name.
لا شيء سوى الاسم.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
The so-called greatest poison master
ما يسمى أعظم سيد السموم
can't even cure his own brother.
لا يستطيع حتى علاج أخيه.
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
Truly ridiculous.
سخيف حقا.
No need for the State Preceptor to worry.
لا داعي للقلق يا سيدي المشرف.
Without our Mo Cheng's gu worms,
بدون ديدان جو مو تشنغ،
how would Nan Zhengci have so many rotting soldiers?
كيف يمكن لنان تشنغشي أن يمتلك هذا العدد الكبير من الجنود المتعفنين؟
You and your white-haired freak brother
أنت وأخوك الغريب ذو الشعر الأبيض
wouldn't have survived till now.
لم يكن ليبقى على قيد الحياة حتى الآن.
Show some respect.
أظهر بعض الاحترام.
Or I'll turn you into rotters too.
أو سأحولك إلى تعفن أيضًا.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
This disguise technique lasts only three days.
تستمر تقنية التمويه هذه لمدة ثلاثة أيام فقط.
If we don't find Master Bukku by then
إذا لم نتمكن من العثور على ماستر بوكو بحلول ذلك الوقت
and rescue everyone,
وأنقذ الجميع،
you must leave as well.
يجب عليك أن تغادر أيضاً.
Get out!
اخرج!
Didn't expect the princess to have such a temper.
لم أتوقع أن الأميرة لديها مثل هذا الغضب.
Out!
خارج!
Tomorrow night, you'll be mine.
غدا في الليل، سوف تكون لي.
My second brother is conspiring with you.
أخي الثاني يتآمر معك.
But the people of Xuan Cheng
لكن شعب شوان تشنغ
won't forget the evil Mo Cheng did
لن أنسى الشر الذي فعله مو تشنغ
They will never forget
لن ينسوا أبدا
Neither will I
انا ايضا لن افعل
I promise you’ll end up with nothing
أعدك أنك لن تحصل على أي شيء في النهاية
The once fragile little princess
الأميرة الصغيرة الهشة ذات يوم
has grown up now
لقد كبرت الآن
W-What did you say?
س- ماذا قلت؟
If the old Lord were still here
لو كان الرب القديم لا يزال هنا
he’d be proud of the princess’s change
سيكون فخوراً بتغيير الأميرة
Princess Zhengyue, it’s me
الأميرة تشنغيو، أنا
Master Dong Qing, is it really you?
سيد دونغ تشينغ، هل هذا أنت حقًا؟
Princess Zhengyue
الأميرة زينجيو
We can’t let Nan Zhengci keep making mistakes
لا يمكننا أن نسمح لنان تشنغشي بالاستمرار في ارتكاب الأخطاء
We must stop him
يجب علينا ايقافه
I came here today
لقد جئت هنا اليوم
to ask for your help
لطلب مساعدتك
But I’m so useless
ولكنني عديم الفائدة تماما
What can I even do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل حتى؟
You’re the only one who can do this
أنت الوحيد الذي يمكنه فعل هذا
Xuan Cheng’s future is in your hands
مستقبل Xuan Cheng بين يديك
Zhu Sheng, Zhu Sheng
تشو شنغ، تشو شنغ
Princess Zhengyue
الأميرة زينجيو
Why are you in such a hurry?
لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
I have something important to tell you
لدي شيء مهم أريد أن أخبرك به
Dong Qing isn’t dead
دونغ تشينغ لم يمت
He’s pretending to be the State Preceptor of Mo Cheng
إنه يتظاهر بأنه المرشد الرسمي لمو تشنغ
He and Fengwu Zhou are plotting to harm my second brother
هو و فينغوو تشو يتآمران لإيذاء أخي الثاني
What?
ماذا؟
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
It’s true
إنه صحيح
He just came to me under the pretense of delivering my wedding dress
لقد جاء إليّ بحجة تسليم فستان زفافي
He wants me to cooperate with their plan
يريدني أن أتعاون مع خطتهم
Though I resent my brother marrying me off to Mo Cheng
على الرغم من أنني مستاءة من زواج أخي من مو تشنغ
he’s still my real family
إنه لا يزال عائلتي الحقيقية
I won’t truly betray him
لن أخونه حقا
If you don’t believe me
إذا كنت لا تصدقني
go check the Mist Cave
اذهب للتحقق من كهف الضباب
The body inside
الجسم في الداخل
will show you if it’s Dong Qing or not
سأريك ما إذا كان دونغ تشينغ أم لا
Dong Qing is right here
دونغ تشينغ هنا
Princess Zhengyue lied to me
كذبت الأميرة Zhengyue علي
She didn’t lie to you
هي لم تكذب عليك
State Preceptor
مشرف الدولة
You all
أنتم جميعا
Why are you together?
لماذا انتم معا؟
Are you trying to double-cross each other?
هل تحاولون الغش على بعضكم البعض؟
Enough talk
كفى كلاما
Take me to Master now
خذني إلى المعلم الآن
Dong Qing
دونغ تشينغ